{
    "subject": "resource/The_Last_Stand_(album)",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Album",
    "human_readable": "The Last Stand (album) is an album.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8131065964698792,
            "question": "What year was the album 'The Last Stand' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7545297741889954,
            "question": "Has the album 'The Last Stand' received any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.704156219959259,
            "question": "Who is the artist or band behind the album 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6561543345451355,
            "question": "Can you name any songs on the album 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6358669400215149,
            "question": "Are there any notable collaborations on the album 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6234295964241028,
            "question": "Where could someone listen to the album 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6094380021095276,
            "question": "What is the overall theme or mood of the album 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.360154390335083,
            "question": "Is 'The Last Stand' a musical piece?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32281941175460815,
            "question": "In what genre would you classify the music on 'The Last Stand'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20379598438739777,
            "question": "What type of creative work is 'The Last Stand'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Last Stand (album) is an album.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2973_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what genre would you classify the music on 'The Last Stand'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2973_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Last Stand' a musical piece?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2973_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall theme or mood of the album 'The Last Stand'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2973_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2973_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The information in the documents confirms that \"The Last Stand\" is indeed an album by Swedish power metal band Sabaton, released on August 19, 2016. This matches the query statement, so the output value is \"yes\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The Last Stand\" is Sabaton's eighth studio album, which supports the triple stating that \"The Last Stand (album) is an album.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}